我们刚刚看到了如何将存储在计算机上的文件中的图像加载到MATLAB中
We have just seen how we can load images from files stored on our computer into the MATLAB
我们可以开始观察它们并操纵它们的环境，但对于机器人来说
environment where we can begin to look at them and manipulate them, but for a robot
它正如现在一样感知世界，这一点非常重要。所以那些信息
it is really important that it is sensing the world as it is now. So information that
存储在文件中可能不是最新的。我们需要把世界看作它
is stored in a file may not be sufficiently up to date. We need to see the world as it
现在是：我们需要能够从相机中提取图像。
is now: we need to be able to bring images in from a camera.
现在很幸运的是，几乎所有的计算机都连接了一个或多个摄像头
Now it is really fortunate today that almost all computers have one or more cameras attached
给他们。所以我们现在要看的是我们如何从相机获取信息
to them. So what we are going to look at now is how we get information from a camera on
我的电脑进入MATLAB环境。所以我们在MATLAB桌面工作区
my computer into the MATLAB environment. So here we are in the MATLAB desktop workspace
再次，为了从相机中抓取图像，我们首先创建一个对象，一个MATLAB
again and in order to grab an image from a camera we first create an object, a MATLAB
连接到相机的物体，在这种情况下，它是第0相机
object that is attached to the camera and in this case, it is the zeroth camera—that
是我的电脑第一台相机。它在MATLAB中创建了一个新对象
is the first camera that my computer has. And it creates a new object in the MATLAB
workspace，VideoCamera类型的对象。一旦创建了这个对象，就可以了
workspace, an object of type VideoCamera. As soon as this object has been created, the
连接到我电脑的相机已经上线了;一点点红色的记录灯来了
camera attached to my computer has become live; a little red recording light has come
上。该对象支持许多方法，并且是我们目的最重要的方法
on. This object supports a number of methods, and the most important method for our purposes
是抓取方法，从相机抓取图像，最近的图像来自
is the grab method, which grabs an image from the camera, the most recent image from the
相机，并显示它。我们可能对实际推杆感兴趣
camera, and displays it. We might be interested in actually putting
将图像转换为工作空间变量，我们就是这样做的。我们分配输出
the image into a workspace variable and we do it in this way. We assign the output of
工作空间变量的抓取方法，在这种情况下，变量im和图像
the grab method to a workspace variable and in this case, the variable im, and the image
从相机中抓取并放入该工作空间变量中。如果我调用该函数
is grabbed from the camera and placed into that workspace variable. If I call the function
再次它将拍摄另一张照片并以不同的姿势显示它。
again it will take another picture and display it with my head in a different pose.
相机正在连续运行。为了关闭相机，我需要销毁
The camera is running continuously. In order to turn the camera off I need to destroy the
相机对象。你可以使用MATLABclear命令执行此操作，因此如果我从中清除对象
camera object. You do that with a MATLAB clear command, so if I clear the object from the
工作空间对象被破坏，相机关闭。红灯消失。
workspace the object is destroyed and the camera is turned off. The red light disappears.